I'm going to make a mistake on purpose.
It's a mess.
Hello.
I've been doing this for a year since
the beginning of the energy dance.
It's a special outfit that starts with
the jersey.
I've never seen such an arrangement.
I think there are various memories.
I think the members who are out more
than the viewers remember various
things.
This time, I made a quiz from the
previous quiz.
The first question is 7 questions. The
second question is 7 questions. The
third question is 6 questions.
I'm the third.
Thank you.
I'll give you a quiz.
I got it.
Let's get started.
I'll start with the first question.
The first question.
Who was the first member to gather on
the train when he suddenly called an
idol and made him sweaty?
Who is it?
I'm the first.
I don't know his name.
I'll start with Hazuki.
Miu Mizutani.
Freddie Mercury.
I'm the first.
I have a question.
Is there anyone who draws pictures?
Who drew the picture?
Hinano, Miu, and Yuna.
Why are you here?
Let's draw the faces of the members
here.
The correct answer is only Hazuki.
I'm frustrated.
The second question.
It's the same video.
You guys chose your own acrostic poem.
What was your acrostic poem?
It was a difficult one.
I did it well.
Wait.
What was it?
I'm sorry.
I'll start with Hazuki.
Saibi Yusyu.
It's like that.
It was like that.
I did it wrong.
Kita Mirin.
It's totally different.
I don't know the difference.
You said Kita Beauty, but you said
Beauty Naya.
I made a mistake.
The correct answer is Kousai Datsumon.
Kousai Datsumon?
Kousai Datsumon.
Don't say that.
What about Mirin?
From here.
The third question.
When an idol tries to do a backflip, an
accident happens.
They practiced doing a backflip before
doing a backflip.
But one of them couldn't do it.
Who couldn't do it?
I did a backflip.
I know.
I was looking at you.
Let's start with Hazuki.
Karen.
Please subscribe to our channel!
You are cute!
You are correct!
Question 4
What is the name of the maid cafe that
you went to?
The name of the maid cafe is easy to
remember because it is characteristic.
What should I do?
Hazuki-san, please.
Nyanpontan.
I got it.
Correct.
You got it right.
Question 5.
I played Glico at a haunted spot.
Where is the haunted spot where Miyagi
went?
Two people went there.
I don't remember.
Hazuki-san, please.
Hagoromo Shrine.
Hanabushi Shrine.
I got it.
Who is it?
It's a name of a person.
What is that?
It's not.
What is it?
I didn't hear it.
I'll ask you.
It's a place where you can go up the
stairs of Yamagata.
I wanted to go there.
Wait a minute.
I got it.
I'm a genius.
Fujita-san, please.
I don't know.
Question 6.
I think you cooked together at a
community center.
Is there a member who never had a knife
when cooking?
Who is it?
Let's start with Saki.
Shinju-chan, Aiba-chan, Hitoshinju,
Hitoshinju.
Except Fujitani-san.
Wait, who is Misai Hitoshinju?
Misai Hitoshinju is not Misai.
It's Mitsui.
And, what is Hitoshinju?
It's probably Hitoshinju.
I got confused.
Misai Hitoshinju.
The last question.
Question 7.
We have a fun book, do you know it?
I've heard of it recently.
Who helped Abekatsu-san to write the
book, and corrected it to a nice poem?
I can write it without knowing it.
Saki-san, please.
Kaya.
Date-san.
It's not Beiyan, it's Kayan.
Good.
It was good.
It was like a corn.
Why was it like that?
It was scary.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Next is intermediate level.
Level up! It's difficult.
The first question.
Let's check the limit of the speed
phone.
How many meters was the limit?
1 meter is this much.
What was it?
Let's start with Matsuki.
The speed was 80,000 yen.
300 meters.
270 meters.
That's it.
Disgusting!
The correct answer is 180m.
What?
It's close.
It's true.
If I pull it, it's close.
What?
It's the other way around.
Shiro-chan!
Question 2.
Who ate dried plums twice in a row in
the 100th game?
Can everyone answer it right away?
I'm getting old.
Okay, let's start with Tatsuki.
Karen.
Hikaru.
I'm tired.
Only Fujitani.
I was a little confused.
Question 3.
We divided into teams during the
cooking competition.
What did Fujitani put out of the box at
that time?
What is a box?
Everyone first.
It's a hint.
When we divided into teams.
I see.
From Hazuki.
It's a kibiru-hapo-kyun.
Correct.
I got it.
You are good at it.
Question 4.
We did a general knowledge test.
What did Tachibana answer as the top 3
in the world?
What was it?
I saw it on TikTok.
It's like that.
Mon was not there at that time.
I think I heard it later.
I was quite right.
I should've answered it.
Next, from Kazuki.
Shark, whale, anago, snake, beast,
mabushi.
Three?
All of them.
What was it?
The answer is hado, mabushi, anago.
Mabushi is right, anago is right too.
Hado.
Whale, hado.
Question 5.
Do you know what is the ingredient that
Date Fujitani sprinkled on meat and
eggplant?
What was it?
I know.
I had it at home.
This is it.
From Kazuki.
Turmeric powder, cannabis, bonito
flakes.
It's from Kazuki.
I was right.
It's like curry.
Yes.
It's curry with turmeric.
Question 6.
Eat 4kg of strawberries.
While eating, you two sing 2 songs of
Tohoku.
Please write 2 songs.
This is easy.
This is our song, so please write it
without mistake.
What? Our song?
That's terrible.
Is it a word?
I think the song title is kanji or
English.
I can't.
I decided and Truffy girl.
I decided and straight Asu girl.
Is English okay?
Wait, is my English correct?
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I decided.
Straight.
Fujitani and Sakura are correct.
I didn't see the English translation.
Thank you.
Please edit it.
The last question.
This is a reproduction question.
I will reproduce the main scene of the
main drama.
I like it.
What is the line that Hichise said?
Please answer while moving.
I remember the movement.
Karen's impact is great.
And Rine.
Shinjyu.
I will answer.
The truth is only one.
It's you.
What are you doing?
Let's get started.
Yay!
I'm sure I'm doing it right.
I was trying to look at you two and
take a picture.
I couldn't do it at all.
Please subscribe to our channel!
What is he writing?
I think it's something like that.
I think I got it.
The answer is...
We will show you the video.
Please watch the video.
The incident does not happen in the
conference room.
It happens on the spot.
When you digest the sentence, put your
finger on your shoulder and point your
finger forward.
The incident does not happen in the
conference room.
It's difficult.
I'm disappointed.
I don't know how to use it.
It's difficult.
Zuran
This is a difficult one.
The first question.
Zuran
When an idol tries to turn the tables,
she gets into a big accident.
Fujitani, who is physically strong,
says that she and she are the only ones
who get into a big accident when she is
flexible before the lesson.
Who is the other physically strong
member?
I think I should write down the
physically strong member.
The members will know the answer if you
watch the video.
I've been watching it for years.
I'm sure I know the answer.
Let's start with Honzuki.
Shinju
The other side.
The answer is Flip.
Junshin
Yay!
The second question.
Zuran
This is a video recorded in Yamabuya.
I told you that I was going to climb a
mountain for the first time in front of
the station.
At that time, there was a member who
collapsed.
Please answer all of them.
What?
I know the answer.
Can you tell me how many people?
No hint.
To be continued.
Kanae, Yuna, Waka, Hirano, Miyu, Kaya
I think I'm going to collapse.
Me and Yuna
Hirano, Waka, Miyu, Yuna
All of them
The answer is
Izura-chan
I'm not going to collapse.
It's rare.
I miss it.
I fell down on purpose to collapse.
It's a mess.
Question 3
How many swords did you hide from
E-Beans in the battle of the century?
I don't even know myself.
If you remember, you are watching it.
Only Fujitani
Did you remember that?
I remembered.
I counted the places where I put them.
That's great.
I couldn't get all of them.
Question 4
If you were to be a regular at a high
school, would you take the exam?
An interview
Please answer the name of the high
school that Sakura-san wrote in her
diary.
I'm not sure if it's a high school that
Mon-chan wrote.
Which one is it?
I don't want to say.
Kajiki-san
Harvard High School
Igigari High School
It's a pity, but
All of them
Iwate Prefecture Igigari High School
Iwate Prefecture?
All of them?
Question 5
It's the same word.
Please answer the name of the license
that Sakura-san is currently studying
and the year of study.
Year of study?
Why?
It's a diary, so you should know the
places where you wrote it.
I remembered!
I'm confident.
Kajiki-san
I got a cooking license in May 2017.
I want to get it.
I got a license to make people smile in
May 2004.
Kajiki-san and Sakura-san
It's a wonderful license.
I've been studying alone since I was
born.
I see.
The last question.
The sixth question.
Which one looks like Fujita?
I see.
What was the dance of Date Samba?
What was it?
Let's do it one by one.
Question 6
I'll start.
Please give me a high rating.
This atmosphere is crazy.
I thought so, too.
You don't do it.
I do it alone.
I'm a cheater.
You are like a squid.
I don't do it.
This is different from the quiz.
Who has thought about it?
I know.
Do you write it?
Let's see.
Yasumori.
Ruin.
Only you and Fujita.
That's all.
Did I get it right?
Please subscribe to the channel.
The winner of this game is...
Shiki-san go see you
with 10 points!
Actually, I am 9, too.
Don't you think it's a joke?
You guys know each other...
Thank you for watching
Suzuki بنたん all year long!
I'm going to change my mind.
Please.
I'm going to eat everything.
I'm going to die.
Please.
Bye bye!